在上一集里
Previously on "Transformers Prime"...
既然我能统治两个世界…
Why rule only one world when I can rule two?
威震天已经完成了数字化地球的第一阶段
Megatron has managed to accomplish the first phase of his cyberforming of Earth...
建造他的堡垒
the construction of his fortress.
在贾斯帕 内华达？
In Jasper, Nevada?
我不明白 他们干嘛要建在这儿？
I don't get it. Why here?
因为霸天虎已经发现了我们基地的位置
Because the Decepticons have discovered the location of our base.
上吧 我的舰队！进攻！
Come, my armada, attack!
基地已经沦陷了
The base is lost.
我们只有分散开才能成功突围
We must disperse to avoid capture.
特工福勒呼叫防空指挥部
Special Agent Fowler to Air Defense Command.
我需要紧急战斗支援
I need immediate combat support.
不！
No.
进行地毯式搜索！
Leave no stone unturned.
主人 看看我们找到了什么
Master, look who we found
从飞船残骸中抓到的雷霆救援队员
pulled from the wreckage of his ship...
千斤顶
Wheeljack.
这么说 有一个死里逃生了
So, one survived.
把我们的“贵客”带回大本营候审 带他回黑山
Take our guest back to the citadel for questioning. Back to Darkmount.
新时代的序幕已经拉开 我的君王
This is the dawning of a new age, my liege...
威震天的王朝开始了
the reign of Megatron.
你很能说会道啊 红蜘蛛
You do have a way with words, Starscream.
快点
Make haste and unearth the Autobot corpses.
卓天越之锤？
The forge of Solus Prime?!
你们有本事找得到这个
How is it that you have managed to materialize that
却搜不出一具汽车人的残骸？！
yet not the remains of a single Autobot?!
快回答主人的话
Answer your Lord and master.
他们的尸体在哪里？！
Where are their bodies?!
你伤得重吗？
You're hurt
但你看上去要比你的实际情况还要糟
but you probably look way worse than you feel.
不 别动也别说话
No, don't move or talk.
保存力量 恢复体力
Just power down. Get your strength back.
我会保护你的
I got you covered.
显然汽车人在我们摧毁基地前就利用环陆桥逃走了
The Autobots clearly ground bridged from their base before it was destroyed.
他们现在可能在任何地方
They could be anywhere.
我们必须启用全球监控 我的陛下
We must initiate global surveillance, my Lord.
派遣清理小队 查遍地球的每个角落
Send search-and-destroy teams to every sector of this planet.
声波 监控所有汽车人的信号传输
Soundwave, monitor all Earth-based transmissions for any sign of Autobot communication...
或是与其人类盟友之间的通讯信号
with each other or with their human counterparts.
主人…
Master...
愚蠢的人类…
Mm. Foolish humans.
我去部署大军
I shall deploy the armada.
没这个必要 红蜘蛛
That won't be necessary, Starscream
何不让敌人尝尝我们的新力量！
not when we can engage our enemy with newfound might.
一个新政权统治了你们的世界
A new power dominates your world.
任何针对我的进一步挑衅行为 我都会加倍奉还！
Any further attempts to attack me will be met with even greater force.
你们的领导人最好明白
Your leaders should be advised
我的融合炮能轻易摧毁任意一个密集居民区
that my fusion cannons possess enough firepower to decimate any densely populated area of my choosing.
我十有八九 会先拿你们的首都开刀
I would, in all likelihood, set sights on your nation's capital, for starters.
明白了 你到底想要什么？
Point taken. Now, what do you want from us?
我什么都不要 福勒特工
Nothing, Agent Fowler.
霸天虎对人类没有恶意
The Decepticons mean no harm to humanity.
我们只是渴望能有个栖身之所
We merely desire a place to call home.
威震天 我无意冒犯
No offense, Megatron, but I'm having a tough time
但我很难相信你的话
swallowing all this...
因为你一心想把人类置于你的魔爪之下！
Since you seem so bent on plastering humankind under molten steel.
福勒特工 我承认战争将我最坏的一面展露无遗
Agent Fowler... I admit that war brings out the worst in me
但我们与汽车人之间的战争已经就此了结
but the conflict with the Autobots is now over
而且我们与人类之间并无瓜葛
and our quarrel has never been with your kind.
既然霸天虎的真正敌人已经不复存在
Now that the one, true enemy of the Decepticons is no more
我唯一的愿望就是能在这个星球上与人类…和平共处
my only wish is to coexist on this planet with the human race, peacefully.
福勒特工 你我携手
Together, Agent Fowler
这梦想定能成真
I believe that you and I can make that dream a reality.
您也蛮会忽悠的啊 主人
You, too, have a way with words, master.
连我都差点儿相信您了
I almost believed you myself.
地球现在归我们了 红蜘蛛
Earth is our planet now, Starscream
是时候收锣罢鼓了
and we shall finish what we started.
人类绝对想不到在谎言的背后…
Humankind has no idea
等待他们的将是什么
what lies ahead for them.
是的 布莱斯将军
Yes, General Bryce.
特别应急方案G-1000已照计划执行
Special containment protocol G-1000 has been executed as planned.
内华达贾斯帕的疏散行动非常成功
Evacuation of Jasper, Nevada, was 100% successful.
对市民和媒体公布的说辞 是流星雨导致的灾难
As far as its citizens or the media are concerned, the threat was a meteor shower
在其造成的辐射消退前 城镇将持续封锁…
and the town is to remain quarantined until the resulting radiation levels can be dissipated.
长官 任何形式的反击都过于冒险了！
Sir, any form of retaliation would be too risky.
我需要更多的时间！
I just need more time.
好 我明白了…
Yes, I understand.
福勒探员
Agent Fowler
那些医疗物资仍然没有到位 我们有伤员急需…
those medical supplies still haven't arrived. We have wounded men who need...
我已经竭尽全力了 达比护士
doing the best I can, nurse Darby.
我一直忙于应付那群刚上任 一心只想把事闹大的将军们
I've been a little busy juggling a bunch of nuke-happy generals who don't seem to care if they blow Nevada sky-high
还有那个假意向我们示好的霸天虎暴君
and a Decepticon warlord who wants to make nice
只因为汽车人都进了废铁场
now that the Autobots are in the scrapyard...
当然那是威震天的想法 不是我的
Megatron's opinion, not mine.
他对我说了一堆屁话 妄图击垮我们的意志
He's feeding me a load of horse pucky, trying to crush our spirit.
还是没有任何人的消息？
Still no word from anyone?
听我说
Listen
没有消息只能表示核心通讯器在基地被炸平时毁坏了
no contact only tells me that the main comm link went down when the base was pounded into pancake batter.
但是如果我给杰克打个电话…
But if I could just call Jack...
你知道这样做有多危险 汽车人也一样
You know it's too risky. So do the bots.
虎子们可以监测任何手机信号
The Cons could trace any cellphone signal.
那就带我回家
Then take me home.
如果杰克联系不上我 他一定会去那里找我
If Jack can't call, that's where he'll look for me.
贾斯帕已经被虎子彻底封锁 谁都回不去了
Jasper's under complete comm lockdown. Nobody's getting back in there.
只有擎天柱还有他的汽车人能解决这场危机
The only ones who can fix this mess are Prime and his bots.
我敢肯定他们就在某处
I'm sure they're out there
低调行事
keeping a low profile.
一定是这样的！
They got to be.
扫描中…
Scanning.
非预期结果…无汽车人身份识别
Negative. No Autobot recognition.
走了！
Clear.
好险 不过你的喷漆蒙混过关了！
Too close. But your paint job did the trick.
看来子通讯链还没有恢复
The comm sub link is still down.
小蜂
Bee
我明白擎天柱为避免虎子抓到我们 将我们分别传送到不同地点
I realize Optimus sent us all to different locations to make us harder for the Cons to find
但如果我们不知道其他人的位置
but if we don't know where in the world anyone else went
该怎么找到他们呢？！
how are we gonna find them?
你说得对 我们只能继续向贾斯帕前进
Right. Just keep heading toward Jasper...
前往威震天巨大的堡垒
toward Megatron's giant fortress.
从没想到路会这么难走
I never knew there were so many rockies.
神子！
Miko!
不许用手机 你知道规矩的！
No cellphone! You know the rules.
哥们儿 我没给任何人打电话
Dude, I wasn't calling anyone
只是在玩我下好了的游戏
just playing a video game I already downloaded.
对不起 我想我有点儿过于紧张了
Sorry. I guess I'm a little on edge.
我们这是去哪儿 小隔？
Where are we headed anyway, Bulk?
你有什么计划吗？
You got some sort of plan?
我们正按雷霆救援队的标准方案行动
We're following standard Wrecker protocol.
方案是…？
Which is...
这是我们在大战时制定的紧急计划
An emergency plan we followed during the war
如果一位雷霆救援队员被困或是掉队
in case any Wrecker got standard or separated from the unit.
我们总是会在特定地点会合
We'd always rendezvous at the exact same set of coordinates.
老千肯定还活着 他会去那里的！
If Jack is still alive, he'll be there.
别停啊
Don't stop now.
我才刚开始享受呢！
I was just beginning to enjoy myself.
相信我 千斤顶
Believe me, Wheeljack
还有得你受的！
there is more where that came from.
我保证你会乖乖告诉我你同伙的藏身之地
And you will tell me the location of your compatriots...
用什么手段 花多长时间
... no matter what it takes
我都无所谓…
... or how long.
不是说了吗
Like I told you
他们并没有在等我
they weren't expecting me.
也根本没告诉我任何信息
They never bothered to fill me in.
所以你只管继续
So, go ahead.
尽管折腾好了…
Knock yourself out.
威震天陛下 有什么能为您效劳的吗？
How may I serve you, Lord Megatron?
集结一支队伍 立刻飞往塞博特恩
Assemble a team and disembark for Cybertron immediately.
以追捕汽车人为首要任务 同时
While hunting Autobots remains paramount
借此机会 找回在混乱中遗弃在铁堡的遗物
we must not squander the opportunity to recover any Iacon relics left behind in the chaos.
据我们所知
For all we know
擎天柱正躲在某处
Optimus Prime is out there somewhere
谋划着同样的事情…
planning to do the same.
没事了 擎天柱
I-It's okay, Optimus.
我就在你身边 我是烟幕
You're with me... Smokescreen.
我怎么在这里？
How did... I get here?
在我们从基地撤离时 也就是虎子开炮那会儿
When we were evacuating the base, just as the Cons opened fire...
本该轮到我撤离的
It was my turn to ground bridge away.
但我做不到
But I couldn't do it.
我不能让你独自面对威震天的大军
I couldn't let you face Megatron's army alone.
于是我偷偷溜了回来
So, I snuck back.
但基地遭到了攻击
But that's when the blast hit
已经完全坍塌了
and the whole joint came tumbling down.
我设法在虎子来之前利用相位仪把您从废墟中救了出来
But I managed to pull you from the wreckage before the Cons dove in, using the Phase Shifter
相位仪是我…在塞博特恩还是一片混乱中抢回来的
which I... managed to snag in all the confusion back on Cybertron.
呃 很抱歉 我违抗了您的命令…
I'm... I'm sorry I defied your orders.
我们在这里很安全
We're safe here
但是我们身处地下 没人能收到我们的信号
but we're down so deep, no one can pick up our signals.
如果我们想找到救护车的话 得去地面
I'll have to scout above ground if I'm gonna have any hope of finding Ratchet.
没…没用的
No. No hope.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
救护车是唯一能医好你的人！
The Doc's the only one who can get you patched up.
擎天柱…
Optimus.
如果贾斯帕没有被及时疏散
What if Jasper wasn't evacuated in time?
妈妈她可能会受伤
She could have been hurt
或者被虎子抓走
or taken by the Cons.
杰克
Jack...
就算她逃出来了
And even if she did get out
没有我的消息 她也肯定急疯了
she's got to be worried out of her mind not knowing where I am.
杰克 冷静点儿
Jack, calm down.
我们会回到贾斯帕的
We'll get back to Jasper
想办法找到你妈妈
find a way to reach your mother
还有其他队员
and the rest of the team.
留在这儿
Stay here.
可能有虎子跟踪我们
Could be a Con on our tail.
对不起 妈妈
Sorry, mom.
如果情况允许 我一定会打给你的
I'd call if I could.
一条短信应该不会有事吧？
Oh, one text couldn't hurt, could it?
主人！
Master.
派出部队
Send in the troops.
另外 声波
And, Soundwave
为我实时传输现场情况！
I want a live feed.
杰克！
Jack.
“我和阿尔茜在一起 很安全 爱你！”
"With Arcee. Safe. Love you."
福勒探员 杰克还活着！
Agent Fowler, Jack's alive!
糟了！
Scrap.
喔 虚惊一场
Oh... Civilian.
杰克！
Jack!
这下我完蛋了！
I am so toast.
杰克 笑一个
Smile, Jack.
你上霸天虎电视节目了！
You're on Decepticon TV.
主人 我们收到画面了
Master. We have a visual.
到底要多久才能干掉一个汽车人和她的人类宠物！
How long does it take to exterminate a lone Autobot and her human pet?!
这个嘛 依我的经验…
Well, in my experience...
我的话不是疑问句 红蜘蛛！
It's not a riddle, Starscream.
抱歉…
Sorry.
那里！
Over there.
这儿可不是藏身的好地方
Not the best cover.
我们不是来藏身的…
We're not here to hide.
嘿 伙计们
Hey, guys.
加点儿汽油还是柴油啊？
Unleaded or diesel?
赶在他们派援军到达之前 快撤！
Let's roll before they send reinforcements.
伙计们 加把劲 不要偷懒！
Come on, fellas. Put your backs into it.
精锐护甲
The Apex armor.
我们的伟大领袖会很高兴的
Our illustrious leader will be pleased.
仍然没有相位仪的下落吗？
Now, any sign of that Phase Shifter?
我真心喜欢那东西
I really liked that thing.
长官！
Sir.
我的火种源啊…
By the Allspark.
怎么样 还有监控资料留存吗？
Well? Did any of the surveillance data survive?
唉 可惜了
Eh... A shame.
我们本应至少得到阿尔茜和那个人类的逃跑方向…
We might have at least learned the direction in which Arcee and the human fled.
显然我们要改进追捕汽车人的方法
Clearly, we need to improve our methods of hunting Autobots
并巩固我们已经获得的战术优势
and build upon the tactical advantage that we've managed to secure.
威震天陛下
Lord Megatron
我已准备好返回黑山
I am ready to return to Darkmount
而且我敢肯定您看见我的发现后 一定会龙颜大悦的
and I'm certain you'll want to see what I've uncovered.
声波 开启太空桥！
Soundwave, open a space-bridge portal.
我现在迫切需要一个好消息
I find myself in urgent need of good news
所以 击倒
so please, Knockout
拜托你告诉我 找到了什么有用的宝贝
tell me that you found something useful.
有一些东西 我的君王
Some things, my liege.
还有…某个人！
And someone.
他还…活着！
He... lives?
震荡波！
Shockwave.
这正是我所需要的战术优势啊！
Just the tactical advantage I need.